我是奥利弗·奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.
五年里  我被困在地狱一般的小岛上
After five years in hell,
我回来只有一个目标
I have returned home with only one goal--
■
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
拯救我的城市
to save my city.
但我之前的方法还不够
But my old approach wasn't enough.
翻译   冰蓝  SophiaSaaaga  Silence
我得成为另一个人
I had to become someone else.
我得成为另一个存在
I had to become something else.
我得成为绿箭侠
I had to become the Green Arrow.
翻译    西西  Reginamoon  Michale 小暴徒
《绿箭》前情回顾
Previously, on "Arrow"...
媒体把他们称为"幽灵"
The media has been calling them a Ghost.
精轴   噃噃   Avis   精校   陈小圈
这些人是前所未见的
They're like nothing we'd ever seen before.
只要我们一接近他们其中一员
Every time we get too close to one of them,
他们就会用氰化物自杀
they off themselves with cyanide.
时间轴风吹来的那片云  校对 苹果果  Michale
达克那些幽灵  他们是蜂巢的人
Darhk's ghosts, they're H.I.V.E.
一个名叫蜂巢的组织派人杀死了我哥哥
An organization called H.I.V.E. killed my brother.
特效&后期   咖啡Lee   总监   苹果果
那就绑走莱拉  这是你的主意吗  奥利弗
Taking Lyla, that was your idea, Oliver.
当着我女儿的面
In front of our daughter!
你不仅破坏了我们的友情
You didn't just lose my friendship--
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
你还失去了我的信任
You losty respect.
西娅  无论你在经历些什么
Thea, whatever's going on with you,
刺客联盟会知道该怎么做
the League, they'll know what to do.
我们去南达尔巴特
We're going to Nanda Parbat.
为什么我们不告诉我哥哥
Why are we not telling my brother?
因为我们去南达尔巴特不止是为了你
Because you're not the only reason for us going to Nanda Parbat.
-需要帮忙吗  约翰  -没事
- Need a hand, John? - I'm good.
我可是州田径赛100米队员
Varsity track, all state, 100 meters.
-狄格  -费利西蒂
- Dig? - Felicity!
你知道那王八蛋去了哪里吗
You know where this son of a bitch went?
他消失了  所以我们才叫他们"幽灵"
He vanished. We call them Ghosts for a reason.
但是空中支援马上就来了
But I got air support coming in on number two.
交给我吧
I got 'em.
奥利弗
Oliver?
他没事  费利西蒂
He's all right, Felicity.
我们需要目标的位置
We need eyes back on our target.
我能给你们更好的
I'll give you one better than that.
前方六米  我给你们包了份礼物
20 feet ahead. I got one gift-wrapped for you.
感觉就像之前的时光  我们三人
Feels like old times, the three of us.
OG
The OGs.
《暴力大都会》
The Original Gangstas.
不回答问题你别想死
You're not checking out without answering a few questions first.
我去哪儿能找到蜂巢  幽灵背后的指使者是谁
Where can I find H.I.V.E? Who's behind the ghosts?
回答我
Answer me!
狄格
Dig!
他跑了
Now he's gone.
该死
Damn it!
我们需要更多人手在外面  奥利弗
We need more boots on the ground, Oliver.
西娅和劳蕾尔真是选了水疗的好日子
Thea and Laurel picked a fine day for a spa treatment.
就西娅目前的状态  我不确定她能有多大帮助
I don't think Thea would be very much help in the state of mind she's in.
她们去哪里了啊
Where the hell are they, anyway?
我真的很享受跟你练剑  娜莎
I really enjoy sparring with you, Nyssa.
我不是在练习
I'm not sparring.
我知道  所以才很有趣
I know. That's what makes it so much fun.
你知道如果有机会  我不会手下留情
You know I would show you no mercy if given the opportunity.
所以我竭力确保不给你机会
That's why I take great care not to give you the opportunity.
下次我会砍了你的头
Next time I'll take your head off.
大人  来了两个外国人
My liege, two foreigners are here.
其中一个自称是拉斯·厄尔·高福的女儿
One of them claims to be the daughter of Ra's Al Ghul.
不  我就是他女儿
No, I am his daughter.
真是惊喜啊
What a pleasant surprise.
小姑
Sister-in-law.
你们怎么来南达尔巴特了
What brings you to Nanda Parbat?
他们带来了一个棺材  大人
They have a coffin with them, my liege.
棺材
A coffin?
我想要你救活我妹妹
I want you to bring my sister back to life.
不行
No.
你夺走了她的生命
You took her life away from her.
救活她是你的责任
It is your obligation to bring her back.
我没有什么责任
I have no obligations in this house.
你不能擅闯此地
You don't get to waltz in here and demand a cup of tea,
就更别提这无理要求了
Let alone this.
西娅当时没死
Thea wasn't dead.
但莎拉是
Sara is.
-全都因为你  -你要求的事
- Thanks to you. - What you are asking for
很久都没人做过了
hasn't been done in ages' past.
只存在于传说之中
Even then, only in legend.
所以我没要我父亲
Which is why I did not ask my father
用复活泉水救活莎拉
to use the pit to save Sara after she fell.
就算莎拉浸在泉水中
Even if Sara went into the pit,
就算那管用
even if it worked...
从泉水中出来的东西也不再是莎拉
who...what came out of the pit would not be Sara.
劳蕾尔
Laurel,
很抱歉  真的
I am sorry, truly sorry,
但是我的答案是  不
but of course my answer is no.
我知道那有些扫兴
Ok, I know that was kind of a bust,
但最初的绿箭团队回来了  这不是很好玩吗
but wasn't it fun having the original Team Arrow back together?
你不该这样的
You shouldn't have.
从一个幽灵嘴里拔下来的
Got that off one of the ghosts.
他们把氰化物胶囊藏在这里
It's where they hide their cyanide capsules.
看起来像是口腔上部左边的两尖齿
It looks like an upper left bicuspid.
有那么一阵子  我打算当
There was a very brief time where I envisioned a future for myself
牙科保健师
as a dental hygienist.
这是我们最近三个月里最棒的线索
The best lead we've got in the last three months.
DNA测序仪的结果需要点时间
It'll take the DNA sequencer a little bit of time,
所以等待时喝点玛格丽塔吧
so I was thinking margaritas while we wait.
记得我们扳倒幕后者后去的那个地方吗
You remember that place we went after we took down the Dodger?
你觉得呢
Ohh. What do you say?
我们仨好久没有聚一聚了
It's--it's been a while since it was just the three of us.
我得回去陪家人
I've got a family to get back to.
我想他只是需要更多时间
I guess he just needs more time.
时间没起作用
Time hasn't been doing anything.
道歉也没用
Apologies haven't.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
我想说
I'm saying that
我不想继续等他回心转意了
I'm done waiting for him to come around.
真是如鱼得水
Like a fish to water.
你说什么
What did you say?
大家在议论
People gossip.
他们说你是个富家子弟  遇难到了这儿
They say that you're a rich kid who got shipwrecked here.
到处发号施令
Bossing people around, giving orders.
对你来说再容易不过
Must feel just like home to you.
有人跑了
We got a runner!
看着这块地方
All right, watch the field.
得了伙计  我们用轻松的方式解决
Hey! Come on, man, let's do this the easy way.
对啊  没错
Yeah! That's the way.
你准备干嘛  说服他叛降吗
Well, what you going to do, talk him into surrendering?
你该这样
That's how you do it.
你是谁
Who are you?
肯定不是该吃枪子的人
Definitely not someone who deserves to be shot.
顺便说一句  你妻女都不在家
Your wife and kid are out, by the way.
你是谁
Who are you?
放松
Relax.
我是个友人
I'm a friendly.
你是超能力联合调查组的
You're a.R.G.U.S.?
字认得不错  莱拉派我来的
You can read. Lyla sent me.
我妻子七个月前就离开组织了
My wife left the agency seven months ago.
她不可能派你去任何地方
She couldn't have sent you anywhere.
是她还在组里时下的命令
She asked back when she was still with the agency.
我迟了会儿  因为帮助别人
Took me a while, because, well, favors aren't exactly
还真不是我的首要工作
at the top of my to-do list.
给  09年雇用弗洛伊德·罗通复仇的人的身份信息
Here. Id on whoever hired Floyd Lawton to do a hit back in '09.
米娜·法雅德
Mina Fayad?
我们要找到她
We're going to find her.
好消息来了
Well, that's the best part.
昨晚运输安全管理局发现她刚入境
TSA flagged her coming in last night.
从马尔科夫飞来
Flew in from Markovia.
我会把她的行踪告诉你
I'll hook you up with her location.
法雅德女士
Ms. Fayad.
你带来了一位客人
You brought a guest.
我听从了指示
As instructed.
不是我的指示
Not by me.
城市治安维持者的问题比预期的严重
The vigilante problem in this city is greater than anticipated.
你在蜂巢中的搭档让我采取些行动
Your partners in H.I.V.E asked me to take steps.
他看着可不像是个解决问题的人
He doesn't exactly look like a problem solver.
你是干什么的
What do you do?
我玩牌  差不多就是这样
I play cards. Mostly.
或许可以演示一下
Perhaps a demonstration.
真有趣  你竟会主动提议
Funny you should mention.
我正好有个麻烦
I happen to have just the problem.
我命令自己的特工被抓到前就自尽
My operatives are under orders to choose death before capture.
这位先生却没有这样做
This gentleman chose wrongly.
我来不及自杀就被抓住了
They got to me before I could take the counter measure.
他还喜欢找借口
He's also prone to excuses,
对此我非常厌倦
which I find tiresome.
很好
Good.
这是免费赠送的
That one was free.
要除掉绿箭侠和他的同党...
Taking out the green arrow and his friends...
就要花钱了
that'll cost.
成交
Deal.
第四季  第三集
绿 箭
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
我不会放弃
I'm not giving up.
我永远不会放弃
I'm never giving up.
因为你只考虑你自己
Because you're thinking only of yourself.
我希望得到你的帮助
I expected your support.
我还想指望你呢
I was counting on it.
那说明你根本不了解我
Then you never really knew me at all.
那泉水让我父亲长寿
The pit gave my father a long life,
非自然的长寿  远超他应有的寿命
longer than what was natural, and much longer than he deserved.
但他内心变得黑暗  这就是代价
But he paid a dark price for it.
西娅现在无疑也在偿还这代价
A price Thea is no doubt paying now.
连最恶毒的敌人  我都不希望他们承受这些
I wouldn't wish it on my most bitter enemy,
更不要说我的挚爱
let alone my beloved.
我不知道泉水能不能让她复活
I don't know if the pit can bring her back.
马尔科姆说的对...
And Malcolm's right--
如果莎拉复活  我不知道她会变成什么样
I don't know what Sara will be like if it does.
但我现在要做的就是去尝试
But what I do know is that I have to try.
为了什么
To what end?
为了把你的妹妹变成魔鬼吗
To have your sister return to you a monster?
她的灵魂...
Her spirit--
我们都深爱的  她的灵魂...
The part that we both love--
我必须相信也会一同复活
That's the part that I have to believe will come back.
你做这些不是出于爱
You're not doing this out of love;
而是出于悲痛
you're doing this out of grief.
我也怀念莎拉
I miss Sara, too.
但她已经离开了  劳蕾尔
But she is gone, Laurel.
永远离开了
Forever.
我已经接受了
I have accepted it.
我觉得你也该去接受
I think it's time you did, too.
还想成为牙科保健员吗
Still wishing you were a dental hygienist?
更像是分子生物学家
More like a molecular biologist.
看到这个了吗
You see this?
没
No.
我要申辩一句  我生物挂过科
In my defense, I flunked biology.
我得过A+  但我还是不明白
Well, I got an A+, and I still have no idea
这是怎么回事
what the hell is going on here.
这DNA只有一半的遗传标记
This DNA has half of the genetic markers that it should have.
一半
Half.
-怎么可能  -不可能
- How is that possible? - It's not.
这人应该是一堆粘液才对
This guy should be nothing more than a pile of goo.
现在怎么着
What now?
里奇菲尔德大道  汽车配件店发生抢劫
Robbery, auto parts store, Litchfield Ave.
打电话给狄格  让他到那里跟我汇合
Call Dig, tell him we'll meet him there.
你去处理抢劫案有点大材小用
Ahh, hold-ups are a little below your pay grade.
确定不要星城警察来处理这案子吗
You sure you don't want the SCPD to handle this one?
最近警察处理问题的效率有多高
How effective have the police been at solving the city's problems recently?
有道理
That's a good point.
费利西蒂 来电
约翰还是不接电话
John's still not answering his phone.
我不会有事的
I'll be fine.
我还是不喜欢你单枪匹马
Still, I don't like you going out there without back-up.
我不是单枪匹马  我还有你
I'm not. I have you.
你刚才表现出的克制
That restraint showed back there?
给我藏起来
Bury it.
这些废物只懂暴力
Violence is the only thing these losers understand.
有些人接受不了
Guys out here can't handle that,
要么迷失  要么吸毒
and they either wash out or end up doing the product.
两种都可以用一枪爆头解决
Both of which are fast-tracks to a bullet in the head.
那些产品  瑞特没跟我说太多
The product-- Reiter hasn't told me a lot about it.
他叫它大满贯
He calls it "Slam."
一种基因改良的混合物
A genetically modified hybrid.
一半是罂粟  一半是古柯叶
One part heroin poppy, one part coca leaf.
一点就能让你爽翻天
Gets you higher than the empire state.
康克林  出事了
Conklin! We got a problem.
有些大满贯不见了  一整块都失踪了
Some Slam's missing. A whole cake.
这个逃跑的只是障眼法
The runner was just a distraction.
知道是谁干的吗
Any idea who did it?
好吧
All right, then.
把他们集合起来
Round them up.
你要干什么
What are you going to do?
我说过了  这里的人只能用暴力对付
I told you, there's only one thing these losers respond to.
趴在地上
Get on the ground.
谢谢你过来
Thanks for coming, by the way.
法雅德女士不确定这能不能行
Ms. Fayad wasn't sure it would work,
不过我知道你不会放过这种经典的抢劫
but I knew you couldn't turn down a good old-fashioned robbery.
你准备好结束了吗
You ready to call this yet?
现在你可以喊结束了
Now you can call it.
游戏还没结束呢
The game's not over yet.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
除了你完全没帮助我朋友这点吗
Aside from the fact that you won't help my friends?
我不会帮助莎拉的
I wouldn't be helping Sara.
你应该最清楚
As you know more than anyone.
你怎么看出来的
What gave me away?
当我在劝说劳蕾尔  跟她说泉水的作用时
When I was cautioning Laurel about the effects of the pit,
我看到了你的眼神
I saw the look on your face.
你也感觉到了  不是吗
You're feeling it, aren't you?
嗜血的欲望
The blood lust.
我身上到底发生了什么
What's happening to me?
泉水能感应到
The pit contains traces of the souls of all the men
所有用它救命的人
and women who have bathed in its waters.
泉水能救命  也能夺命
And what those waters restore, they can also take.
一命换一命
Life for live.
你想说什么
So what are you saying?
你得满足这种欲望
That you need to feed this impulse.
你得服从它
Give into it.
一旦你这么做了  欲望会消退一段时间
Once you do it, it will subside for a time.
好吧
Ok.
我大开杀戒就行了
I'll just go on a killing spree.
谢谢你的为父建议啊
Thank you for the fatherly advice.
难道你就不能
Can you just, for a--a second,
假装自己是个正常父亲吗
pretend to be a normal father?
你不能做到吗  爸爸
Can you do that, dad?
你就不能给我点稍微正常的建议吗
Do you have anything remotely normal to offer me?
好吧
All right.
高山上有个东西
There is something high in the mountains.
一个人
A man.
他们说他是圣人
Some call him a sage.
他会一些古老的疗法
He has a way with the ancient arts of healing.
也许他能帮你
He may be able to help you with this,
但是我不确定
though I am not sure.
这建议正常吗
Does that qualify as being normal?
算正常了
Normal enough.
休息一下吧
Get some rest.
天一亮我们就走
We'll start at first light.
疼吗
This hurt?
-有点疼  -很好
- Yes, it stings. - Good.
这就是你试着单挑超能力者的下场
That's what you get for trying to take on a Meta all by yourself.
-超能力者  -没错
- A Meta? - Yeah.
中城有一个超能力者失踪了
It turns out Central City is missing one.
杰瑞米·特尔
Jeremy Tell.
西斯科说我们可以叫他双倍下注
Cisco says we should call him Double Down,
我不太明白
which doesn't exactly make sense,
因为出事的时候他是在纹身
since he was getting a tattoo when the dark matter wave hit.
你今晚错过了一场好戏
You missed quite a show tonight.
抱歉没帮上你
Sorry I couldn't help out.
-说来话长  -我的天
- It's a long story. - Oh, my god,
没什么说来话长的
it is not a long story.
这事再简单不过了
It is the shortest story in history.
两个人没有帮手就去单挑罪犯
Two guys go take on criminals without asking for back-up
结果差点丧命
and nearly get killed in the process.
我之前什么都没说
You know, I haven't said anything up till now,
因为我一直希望你们俩
because I was hoping that the two of you
能够自己解决这摊烂事
would remove your heads from your own asses without assistance.
看来我错了
Turns out I was wrong.
-别说了  -我就说  你们给我听好了
- Hey! - No, no! This is the part where I talk and you two listen.
你们俩今晚差点就被人杀了
The both of you nearly got killed out there tonight
因为你们没有对方做援手
because you didn't have each other's backs.
这就是偶尔一次而已  费莉西蒂  不会再发生了
That was a one-time deal, Felicity, it won't happen again.
这我同意
I absolutely agree.
因为你们俩要坐下来谈谈
Because the two of you are going to sit down here
直到把话说开
until you have resolved your issues.
听明白了吗
Do we have an understanding?
-我...  -听明白了吗
- I-- - Do we have an understanding?!
明白了
Yeah.
我要把这个拿给帕尔默科技的一个家伙
I'm going to take this to a guy at Palmer Tech
搞清楚这个疯子是怎么把纹身变成致命武器的
to find out how some lunatic Meta turns tattoos into lethal weapons.
如果我回来时你们还没说清楚
If you two haven't figured out your issues by the time I get back,
我就找一群米拉库鲁军人把你们暴扁一顿
I'm going to find a bunch of Mirakuru soldiers to knock some sense into you.
已经好几个月了  伙计
It's been months, man.
我不知道说了多少次对不起
And... I—I don't know how many apologies.
约翰  你不是个小家子气的人
John, you're a forgiving person--
奥利弗  这跟气度无关
Oliver, this isn't about forgiveness, man.
我不知道要怎么看开
I don't know how to move forward with this--
要怎么继续合作
us doing what we do.
我回来之后咱们不是合作得挺好的吗
We've worked fine since I got back.
那是运气好
We got lucky.
奥利弗  曾经有段时间
Oliver, there was a time
我是愿意为你挡子弹的
I would have taken a bullet for you.
现在我可能不会了
And I don't know if I would do that now.
所以就算我们一起出去执行任务
Which means that even when we're out there,
我们也不算是在合作
we are not out there together.
你越界了  伙计
You crossed a line, man.
而你可能还会越界的事实
And the fact that you could do that again
一直在我脑子里徘徊
sits in the back of my head somewhere.
我明白了  我明白了
I get it! I get it.
我明白自己越界了
I understand that I crossed a line.
我明白自己失去了你的信任
I understand that I lost your trust.
但我不明白的是
What I do not understand
你为何不给我个机会重新赢回你的信任
is why you won't give me a chance to earn it back.
你觉得今晚这个超能力者和达克有关吗
You think this meta tonight is connected to Darhk?
我不知道
I don't know.
他提到了一个新成员
Uh...he mentioned a new player,
一个女人  法雅德
a woman. Uh, Fayad.
我们得走了
We need to go.
去哪里
Where?
去个我要尝试再次信任你的地方
Some place where I'm going to try to trust you again.
我喜欢把我们大家看作是一个团队
I like to think of all of us as a team.
而队友间需要相互信任
Teammates need to trust each other.
但如今  我有点做不到
Right now, I'm having a little difficulty doing that.
你们中何不出来个人告诉我谁偷了货呢
Why don't one of y'all tell me who stole the product,
不然这个人就要吃枪子儿了
or else this man right here is going to eat a bullet.
没人说吗
Nobody?
我们再试一次
Let's try this again.
等等  等等
Hey! Wait! Wait, wait, wait.
你说过这些人只能用暴力对付
You said the violence is the only thing these people respond to.
但是看起来不管用啊
Well, it doesn't seem to be working.
那你有什么办法  骂人吗
Well, what do you have in mind? Harsh language?
我在这个岛上待了三年
I've been on this island three years,
学到了一些东西
I've learned some things.
学到什么
About what?
痛苦
Pain.
啊喔
Uh oh.
当你老总走进来时你可不会想说这个词
Those aren't the words you want to say when your CEO walks into a room.
严格来说  "啊"和"喔"可不是词
Well, technically "Uh" and "Oh" aren't words,
它们只是个感叹...
they're interjections--
拜托你告诉我这些是我们
Please tell me these are the prototypes
改变世界的新科技的样机
for our new world-changing technology.
既然它们是我发明的
Well, since I'm inventing them,
那它们难道不应该是我的...
wouldn't that make them my--
这是什么
What is this?
隐形眼镜  内置高清放映
Contact lenses with built-in HD displays.
真厉害  也够快的啊
Whoo, that's impressive, and fast.
准备卖多少钱
How much would they sell for?
十万
Hundred thousand.
十万美元
Hundred thousand dollars?
一副
Per lens.
没事吧
Everything ok?
没事  我的手机老是出毛病
Yeah, my phone just keeps acting up.
我得重启一下
I'm going to restart it.
这是什么
Ooh, what's this?
这是个自主通讯设备
Uh, this is an autonomous Communications device. Uh...
它很棒  只不过
Which is great, uh, except for the fact
它会自爆
that it spontaneous explodes.
也许你需要点东西
Ok, maybe you need something
把你的注意力从所有这些东西上转开
to get your mind off all this.
我有个兼职小项目
I got a little side project,
帮你放松大脑
Clear your head.
比如去赌博吗
Like gambling?
我需要你全面检查它
I need a full work-up.
这有可能是由某种有机生物材料制成的
It's possible it's made out of some sort of bio-organic material.
我需要知道你所能找出的
I need to know everything
关于它的一切信息
that you can find out about it.
奇怪
Hmm, strange.
这些边缘
These edges.
看起来不像是大批量生产的
Doesn't look mass-manufactured.
你从哪里找到的
Where'd you find it?
赌场
Casino.
你赌博吗
You gamble?
是啊  成天赌  扑克是我的心头好
Oh, yeah, all the time. Poker's my jam.
它毁了我一次出线的机会
It ruined an outside flush for me.
我觉得我的对手出千
I think my opponent was cheating.
所以你想让我检查它
So you want me to check it
找找有没有做记号之类的吗
for evidence of marking or something?
是的  找出任何奇怪之处  不寻常之处
Yeah, anything strange, out of the ordinary.
比如...你玩扑克这一点
Like...you playing poker?
我晚点再来找你
I will check back in on you later.
还有  斯莫克小姐
Oh, and, uh, Miss Smoak,
在扑克里并没有出线这一说
there's no such thing as an outside flush in poker.
那大概就是我输了的原因吧
That's probably why I lost.
还记得在俄罗斯
Remember in Russia,
两年前我们把莱拉救出那个监狱的那次
two years ago when we got Lyla out of that prison?
当然
Of course.
那天晚上  罗通告诉我  我弟弟
That night, Lawton told me that my brother
并不是在一次失控的暗杀中被误杀的
was not collateral damage in a hit gone bad;
他说我弟弟就是目标
That he was the target.
还说自己是被一个名为蜂巢的组织雇用的
And that Lawton was hired by an organization called H.I.V.E.
几周前  当我说拉斯称达克的人为
The other week, you reacted when I said
一个蜂巢的特工时  你有反应
that Ra's called Darhk's men a "H.I.V.E" of operatives.
可能是巧合
Could be a coincidence.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
已安排尸检
最后一页
Last page.
那个女人雇了罗通来杀我弟弟
That woman hired Lawton to kill my brother,
而且我敢打赌
and I'm betting
是她雇了那个要杀你的超能力者
she hired that meta that tried to take you out.
理由呢
Based on what?
她叫米娜·法雅德
Her name is Mina Fyad.
两年了  你却没有告诉我
Two years and you didn't tell me.
我俩的共同点比你以为的要多
We have more in common than you think.
奥利弗  那是我第一个合理的线索
Oliver, that's my first legitimate lead.
我得找到她
I have to find her.
法雅德女士给你的任务只有一个
Ms. Fayad hired you for one job.
就一个  不顾我的反对
One. Against my objections,
只因为我的伙伴们太心急
and only because my associates are anxious
想早点开始第三阶段
to progress to phase three.
我们不应该聊这么...
We shouldn't talk about genesis--
别跟我说教什么保密的问题
Don't lecture me about secrecy.
特别是在你刚刚被击败的这一夜
Particularly on the same night that you were just compromised.
-我...  -同时我还失去了一员大将
- I-- - In the same night that I lost good men
就是为了保护你
in the name of protecting you.
-达米恩  -叫我达克先生
- Damian-- - Mr. Darhk!
我觉得我希望再看一次展示
I think I require another demonstration.
怎么  你现在想要我杀了她吗
What, you want me to kill her now?
让我见识见识
Show me.
来杀我
Try to kill me.
我杀了你
I kill you,
还能拿到钱吗
I still get paid?
来吧
Do it.
你是什么东西
What are you?
法雅德女士  蜂巢的很多成员
Ms. Fayad, many members of H.I.V.E.,
觉得我是个江湖骗子
they consider me to be a charlatan.
可这个
But this,
是一种魔术
is a parlor trick.
手上的功夫
Sleight of hand.
这是演示给你看的  特尔先生
This demonstration was for you, Mr. Tell.
让你知道  做了令我失望的事
Just in case you have any doubt as to
会有什么下场
how I process disappointment.
你感觉怎么样
How do you feel?
我感觉
How do I--
我感觉怎么样
how do I feel?
根本就没有圣人
There's no sage.
也没有解药
There is no cure.
从来都没有
There never was.
我很遗憾  你会一直有杀人的冲动
I'm sorry. You will be compelled to kill
直到你杀死了那个伤害了你的人
until you've slain the one who hurt you.
可我做不到
But I can't.
拉斯已经死了
Ok, Ra's is already dead!
那唯一的应对方法
And the only way to cope
就是疯狂地去杀人
is to indulge the blood lust on others.
你
So you--
你把手下派来是给我杀的吗
you just set your men up to be slaughtered?
几周之内你不会再有杀人的欲望了
You will not feel the hunger to kill again for weeks.
不用谢我
No need to thank me.
为了我的女儿
There is nothing I wouldn't do
我什么都会做
to help my daughter.
我想我们都学到了
I hope we learned a lesson of the benefits
与朋友分担麻烦的好处
of trusting our friends with our problems.
你是指你男朋友吗
You mean like your boyfriend?
你本应该表现得比他更成熟
You're supposed to be more evolved than him.
抱歉  但他的确是
Sorry, but he is.
我们能找到她吗
Can we find her?!
找不到  所有的摄像头都没有拍到她
Nope. She's not coming up on any of our traffic or security cams,
不过我还有个好办法
but I think I have the next best thing.
她的手机
Her cell phone,
至少是那个她来星城时
or at least the one that followed her through airport security
跟着她过机场安检的那部
on the way to Star City.
那手机现在在哪
Where's her phone now?
雷德蒙街和第八大街路口
Redmond and Eighth.
你是在哪所豪华的私立学校学到这个的
What fancy private school did you pick this up in?
我在这学的
I learned it here.
在这个岛上生活了三年
Three years on this island,
我受到了各种各样的折磨
and I have been hurt every way you can imagine.
我知道怎么能杀了你  怎么能弄残你
I know what kills, I know what cripples,
还有怎么能弄疼你
and what just hurts.
住手
Stop!
住手  他没有拿那些毒品
Stop! He didn't take the drugs.
是我拿的
I did.
你让我们工作得太辛苦了
You're working us too hard.
有些人很痛苦
And some of the other prisoners are hurt.
我想帮他们止止痛
I wanted to give them something for the pain.
"大满贯"在哪里
And where's the slam now?
都用完了  而且我不会告诉你是给谁用了
It's all used up. And I'm not going to tell you by who.
所以如果你要杀了我
So if you're going to kill me,
赶紧动手吧
just get on with it.
随便你
Suit yourself.
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
你今天已经杀了一个囚犯了
You've already executed one prisoner today.
你要是把劳动力全都杀了
How's Reiter going to feel about you
瑞特会怎么想
exterminating his work force?
我觉得他对小偷会例外的
I think he'd make an exception for a thief.
我会让她消失的
Well, I'd just make her disappear.
把她弄到别的地方
Take her some place.
他们不会找到她的尸体的
They'll never find the body.
好吧  带她走
All right. Take her.
跟他一起
Keep him company.
醒醒
Wake up.
-快醒醒  我们得走了  -什么
- Wake up, we need to go. - What?
-来这里是个错误  -西娅
- It was a mistake to come here. - Thea.
离我远点
Stay the hell away from me.
西娅  怎么了
Thea, what's wrong?
他不会帮莎拉  也不会帮我
He's not going to help Sara and he's not going to help me!
-西娅  -别跟我说话
- Thea! - Don't talk to me!
我只是想帮你
I was only trying to help you.
帮我
Help me?
真是可笑
Yeah, that's funny
不是一般的可笑
on more than a few levels.
我最喜欢的部分就是
My favorite is you are the reason
-你把我害成了这个样子  -我知道
- Why I am like this in the first place. - I know.
我不会再杀人了
I will not kill people.
不会了
I won't!
我不想再见你  离我远点
Stay out of my life and the hell away from me!
我们注定要永远在一起
We are bound together forever.
你和我  父亲和女儿
You and me, father and daughter.
让我证明给你看
Let me prove it to you.
怎么证明
How?
我对莎拉的死负有责任
I am responsible for Sara's death,
而且我也有办法能弥补  至少我尽力去弥补
yet I have the means to make it right, or at least try to.
你觉得在我知道那复活泉水对我的影响后
Do you think after knowing what that Pit has done to me,
我还会让莎拉去用吗
that I would let that happen to Sara?!
我觉得如果你真的想要克服你杀人的冲动
I think if you are truly sincere in fighting your blood lust,
你也会教给莎拉的
you would offer the same to Sara.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
我说我愿意让你的妹妹复活
That I am willing to heal my daughter's conscience
从而让我女儿的良心好过
by restoring your sister's life.
我们应该为仪式
That we should prepare
准备好莎拉的遗体了
Sara's body for the ceremony.
我还能定位到法雅德女士的手机
I'm still getting a ping off Ms. Fayad's cell phone,
前方三米
Ten feet ahead.
约翰
John...
这本是我第一个能得到答案的机会
It was my first chance for answers.
也是最后一个
My last chance.
-抱歉  -不需要抱歉  奥利弗
- I'm sorry. - Don't be, Oliver.
错不在你  在我
This isn't your fault. It's mine.
我本该信任你
I should have trusted you.
早点把这事告诉你
Told you about this forever ago.
要是我说了  我之前就能抓到她
If I had, she wouldn't have gotten away from me earlier.
她也不会死  足矣得到一些答案了
Would be alive, enough now, for some answers.
我们会找到答案的
We're going to get answers.
奥利弗  已经两年多了
Oliver, I haven't been able
我都没法得到答案
to get answers for more than two years now!
这两年多时间
For more than two years...
你一直在单干
you've been doing this alone.
你想让我帮你看一下手机吗  斯莫克小姐
You want me to take a look at your phone for you, Miss Smoak?
我认为我们的工作关系已经到了
I think we've reached the point in our working relationship
你可以叫我费利西蒂的地步了
Where you can call me Felicity.
你没注意到你的名字有多讽刺吗
Have you ever considered how ironic your name is?
费利西蒂这个词是指找到对一个人的思维的
"Felicity" Refers to the ability to find appropriate expression
正确表达方式的能力  但这并不是
for one's thoughts, which is not exactly
你特别擅长的领域
something you're particularly good at.
好吧  你说的没错  就叫斯莫克小姐吧
Yeah, you're right, let's stick with Miss Smoak.
扑克牌上有什么进展吗
Any luck on our playing card?
有  就在这里  费利...
Yeah, it's actually right there, Felic--
斯莫克小姐
Miss Smoak.
只不过这根本就不是一张扑克牌
Except it's not a playing card at all.
据我所知
Now, in my experience,
扑克牌可不包含运动蛋白
playing cards don't contain motor proteins,
本体刺激感受器和神经网络
proprioreceptors and a neural net.
我们该把它交还到
The responsible thing to do would be able
它的合法所有人手里
to get this back to its rightful owner.
有办法追踪到他吗
Is there any way to track him down?
要是能说实话告诉我你是在哪得到它的
Well, if you tell me the truth about where you got it from,
也许能加速这个进程
that could speed along the process.
我说的就是实话
I did tell you the truth.
真的  追踪它的主人吧
I did. Now, tracking the owner?
看到这个墨迹了吗  没别的叫法合适了
You see this ink here, for lack of a better word?
这是磁铁矿  是纹身墨水的主要组成部分
It's magnetite, which is the key component to tattoo ink.
真的吗
You don't say.
没错   并且
I do. I also say that
磁铁矿恰好可以引导鸟类体内罗盘
magnetite happens to guide the internal compass of birds,
例如信鸽
specifically homing pigeons.
那也就是说用扑克牌里面的磁铁矿
So is it possible to use the magnetite in the card
得到牌主的位置信息
to get a location on our
也是可能的
poker player?
理论上是的  然而如果你
Theoretically. Though, if your
假想的扑克对手有一整副这样的牌
hypothetical poker opponent has a deck full of these cards,
他很有可能更快找到你
he'll probably be able to find you faster.
柯蒂斯  我们得
Curtis, we have to--
我来跟你们俩做个交易
I'm going to make you two a deal.
第一个告诉我绿箭侠在哪的人
First one to tell me where you can find the Green Arrow...
可以活命
gets to live.
-绿箭侠  -我有个更好的主意
- Green Arrow? - I have a better idea--
快跑
Run!
斯莫克小姐  我必须知道这是什么情况
Miss Smoak, I really need to know what's going on here!
这里
Here!
董事会知道
Does the board of directors
这栋大厦里有个秘密电梯吗
know there's a secret elevator in the building?
你什么时候变得这么厉害了
Since when are you such a bad ass?
-一直如此  -我有很多问题要问
- Since always. - Ok, I have multiple questions.
好吧  这事儿说来话长
OK, obviously there's a very long explanation to this.
简而言之就是我跟绿箭侠共事
The short version is that I work with the Green Arrow,
这家伙想要杀我  是我们  抱歉
this man is trying to kill me-- well, us, sorry--
我们现在要去的
And I'm taking us down to
是唯一一个能保证安全的地方
the only place that we're going to be safe.
大堂
The lobby?
并不是
Not exactly.
你们还有个隐藏楼层
You have a hidden floor.
在这我们应该是安全的  但以防万一
We should be safe here, but just in case...
我想我知道在哪儿能找到绿箭侠了
I think I know where I can find the Green Arrow.
这意味着不杀你们的那个交易现在失效了
Which means that offer about not killing you is off the table.
待在这  别动
Stay here. Do not move.
-你会用这玩意吗  -不会
- Do you even know how to use that thing?  - No.
柯蒂斯  柯蒂斯
Curtis, Curtis!
费利西蒂
Felicity!
在这呢  在这呢
I'm here, I'm here, OK?
什么情况
What happened?
你们超能力者回来拿他的黑桃A了
Your meta came back to retrieve his ace of spades.
你把他  击退了
And you-- you fended him off?
别表现得这么吃惊
Don't sound so surprised.
好吧  有个同事帮了我一下下
OK, I had a little bit of help from a co-worker,
但说实话  他比我还慌张
but to be honest, he was more freaked out than I was.
-他还好吧  -他没事
- Is he all right? - Yes, he's fine.
我把他送到了星城总医院
I sent him to Starling General.
并且他只知道我的秘密  不知道你的
And he only knows about my secret, not yours.
如果他可以用扑克牌追踪到这里
If he can trace the cards back here,
我们是不是也可以反追踪到他
can we use the cards to trace back to him?
这正是柯蒂斯  我那个被吓坏了的同事
That is exactly what Curtis, my freaked-out co-coworker,
当时正在做的
was doing when...
查到了  他正奔向星城高速公路
I got something. He's headed for the Star City Expressway,
可能是从高速公里回到中城
probably high-tailing his way back to Central City.
真可惜他回不去了
Too bad he's not going to make it.
你们这么做我就杀了你们
I will see you all dead before I let you do this!
拜托了  劳蕾尔
Laurel, please!
别这么做
Don't!
你确定要这么做吗
Are you sure you want to do this?
别停下来
Just keep going.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我跟你说过
I told you--
复活泉水从未用来
The Pit has never been used for--
等一下
No, wait.
看
Look.
莎拉
Sara?
抓住她
Hold her!
莎拉  莎拉
Sara! Sara!
没事的  莎拉
Sara, it's OK.
你会好起来的
You're going to be OK.
没事了
It's OK.
不会有事的
重新命名了城市名以纪念雷蒙德·帕尔默博士
星    城
还没见过你们这么傻的
Well, you guys are a special kind of stupid.
我本想要把小镇炸飞  现在就当打成平手吧
I was going to blow town, call it a draw.
先告诉我们是谁雇你来的
Not until you tell us about your employer.
蜂巢在哪  幕后主使人是谁
Where's H.I.V.E.? Who's behind the ghosts?
快说
Tell me!
知道你们的问题出在哪吗
You know what your problem is?
跟我的雇主相比  你们根本吓唬不了我
You don't scare me half as much as he does.
小心
Look out!
没事吧
You OK?
没事  有防弹衣
Yeah. Kevlar held.
你替我挡了一枪
You took a bullet for me.
那些是
They were...
有超能力者的纹身扑克牌
meta-human tattoo playing cards.
依然算数  奥利弗
Still counts, Oliver.
依然算数
Still counts.
敬一箭队
To OTA.
独一无二的绿箭侠队
Original Team Arrow.
抱歉  我知道你们讨厌我起的这个名字
Sorry, I know you hate it when I call us that.
我越来越喜欢这名字了
It's growing on me.
西斯科把我们的超能力者关在铁山监狱
Cisco has our meta in lock-up at Iron Heights.
但我们还是套不出任何情报
Yeah, we still can't get any intel.
他太害怕达米恩·达克
He's too afraid of Damian Darhk.
我也是  双倍下注会把二号藏身处
Well, so am I. I mean, what are the odds that Double Down
告诉达米恩的几率有多大
told Darhk about lair 2.0?
大到我们该开始考虑三号藏身处了
Enough that we should start thinking about lair 3.0.
我一直在准备一些事
I've been working on something.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
我以为你汲取了教训
I thought you would learn
不再对朋友隐瞒秘密
your lesson about keeping secrets from friends.
不是秘密
It's not a secret.
是惊喜
It's a surprise.
你很喜欢这样是吧
You enjoyed that, didn't you?
折磨那个人
Torturing that man.
你连他的名字都不知道
You don't even know what his name is.
快点走
Walk faster.
伊莱亚斯  他叫伊莱亚斯
Elias. That was his name, Elias.
快点
Faster.
我并不这么急着去死
I am in no rush to get to my death.
我想拉大我们之间的距离
I'm trying to put some distance between us.
我们和理查德之间吗
Between us and Richards?
不  在我们和...
No, between us--
在我们和地雷之间
between us and the landmine.
听我说
Listen to me--
我是不会杀你的
I am not going to kill you,
但是你要相信我
but you need to trust me,
不然我们都会死  明白吗
or we're both dead. Do you understand?
明白
Yes.
好
OK.
没事吧
You OK?
唯一受损的是我的工作室
Oh, well, the only thing wounded is my work space.
如果丹尼斯先生问起
Oh, and if Mr. Dennis asks,
就告诉他之所以变成这样
please just tell him that all this happened
是因为当时我正在做实验
because an experiment I was running
结果完全出乎意料
had an unforeseen outcome.
谢谢你没告诉他
Thank you for not letting him know
地下室有个秘密的藏身处
that there is a secret lair in the basement.
我是个全能的员工
I'm a full service employee.
对于一个差点被超能力者
Well, you seem pretty calm for a guy
杀死的人来说  你还挺冷静的
who nearly got killed by a meta-human.
斯莫克小姐
Miss Smoak,
我来帕尔默科技
I came to Palmer Tech so
是为了帮助你让这个城市变得更美好
I can help make this city a better place.
当得知我的老板也在做同样的事的时候
Can you even imagine how excited I am
你能想象得到我的那种兴奋吗
to know that my boss is doing exactly that?
你真的帮了个大忙  柯蒂斯
Well, you really helped out, Curtis.
没有你  绿箭侠...  我们根本做不到
The Green Arrow-- we couldn't have done it without you.
费利西蒂
斯莫克小姐  没什么事吧
Miss Smoak, is-- is everything ok?
不知道
I don't know.
没事的
It's OK.
一切都会好的
Everything's going to be OK.
老爸肯定不会相信的
Dad's not going to believe it.
他看到你一定会很高兴的
He's going to be so happy when he sees you.
劳蕾尔
Laurel?
没事
It's fine.
你刚从复活泉水出来时
The same thing happened to you
也是这个样子
when you first came out of the Pit.
只是她需要的时间比你久一点
She's just taking longer.
可能是因为她是
It's probably because she was--
劳蕾尔  这方面我们一无所知
Laurel, we are in uncharted waters here.
我建议你做好最坏的打算
I suggest you prepare yourself for the worst.
大人  有情况
My liege, something has happened.
你干了什么
What have you done?!
我父亲不相信任何人
My father was not a trusting man.
所以他设计了一种方法来毁掉复活泉水
He devised a mean to destroy the Pit
免其力量落入恶人之手
should its powers fall into the wrong hands--
比如说你
Like yours.
娜莎  你为什么要这么做
Nyssa, why would you do something like this?
看看你妹妹的样子  你怎么问得出这个问题
How can you even look at your sister and ask me that?
总有一天  我会有机会
One day, I will have my moment,
杀了你
and I will kill you.
而到那时
And now when I do,
没人能再复活
there will be no coming back.
把她拿下
Take her.
我警告过你  劳蕾尔  也求过你
I warned you, Laurel. I begged you.
去年发生在莎拉身上的事的确是马尔科姆的错
What happened to Sara last year was on Malcolm's hands,
但是现在发生在她身上的事
but what's happening to her now
全是你的错
is on yours.